Finding aid for the Alan Mandell papers, 1950-2012 LSC.2123
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Individual Files, 1950-2012
  - Subseries 2.2: Individuals, 1950-2012
    - Gilmour, R., 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Gilcher, Bill, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Gilson, Peggy, 1967-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Glenn, Libbie, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Gluck, Louise, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Goldstein, Sydney (City Arts), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Gombrowicz, Witold, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Gontarski, Stan, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Grassle, Karen, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Green, Frances and Bill, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Gregory, Andre, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Grginovich, Tony, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Guare, John, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Gubaryov, Vladimir, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Gunn, Thom, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Gutierrez, Jose Jr., circa 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Hackett, Jeanie (Classic Lab), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Haines, Fred, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Hammerman, Barbara, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Hansen, John, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Hara, Lil, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Harris, Julie, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Harris, Mark, 1971-1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Havoc, June, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Hawkes, Jack, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Hawkes, John, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Hawkins, Jamie, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Hayes, Marjorie, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Heidt, Ed (Samuel Beckett Materials), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Heimfeld, Leona, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Heinemann, Larry, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Heller, Alfred, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Heller, Elinor, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Hellman, Isaias, 1989-1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Henley, Beth, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Heywood, Anne, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - The Hiding Place (Mark Rucker), 2003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hill, Don, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hirschfeld, Al (Documentary), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Huckenberry, John Russell, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Hoey, Randy, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Hongo, Garrett Kaoru, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Honig, Edwin, circa 1990 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Horovitz, Israel, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Horton, Jerry, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Hotchkis, Joan, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Huddle, Elizabeth, circa 1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Huffman, Fred and Diane, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Hugenberg, Pat Petrie, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Hunt, Mame, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Hunter, Holly, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Iacovelli, John, 1990-2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Imison, Michael, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Infante, Jennifer R., circa 2000 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Irvine Foundation/Vanguard, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Irving, David, 1968-1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Irving, Jules (1 of 3), 1959-1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Irving, Jules (2 of 3), 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Irving, Jules (3 of 3), 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Israel, Irving, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - James, Edmund (Eddie), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Jenson, Julie, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Johnston, Charlotte, 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Jolley, Joe, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Jordan, June, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Kaminskaya, Larissa, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Kaplan, Abbott, circa 1979 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Katsumoto, Ken, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Kazle, Elynmarie, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Keach, Stacy, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Kent Boyd, Louise, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Kershaw, James, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Ketchum, Robert G., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Kierland, J. S. (Playwrights Lab), 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Kim, Jeanie, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Kimbrell, Marketa, 1968-1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kinsella, W. P., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Kitch, Ken, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Kittay, Leo, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Knowlson, Jim (Samuel Beckett Materials), 1992-2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Koehler, Bob, 1992-1997 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Kubzansky, Jessica, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Labell, Harold, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Labell Family, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Lahr, Bert, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Lahr, John, 1986-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Lambert, Lina, 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Langton, Basil, 1984-1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Laramore, Paul, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Lassell, Michael J., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Lavigne, Robert, 1995-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Lear, Robert N., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Leduc, Jean Denis, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Lehman, Leo, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Leigh, Robert, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Leipzig, Adam, 1982-1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Lemelson, Jerome, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Levine, Philip, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Levitow, Roberta, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Levy, John, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Lewis, Kevin, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Lewis, Robert, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Lieberman, Ital, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Liebfried, Rich, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Lifton, Mitchell, 1992-1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Lim, Paul Stephen, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Lindfors, Viveca, 1984-1995 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Lindquist, Kryztov, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Littlejohns, Joanna and Eric Snell, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Literary Stages Los Angeles (Samuel Beckett Materials), 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Lo, Ysa, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Loeb, Jennifer, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Lortel, Lucille, 1977-1997 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Lovely, Shawn, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Luckman, Charles, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Lummis, Suzanne, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Lyons, Morgan, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Lyons, Warren, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Machray, Bob, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Mackenzie, Evan, circa 1990 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Mackley, Paul, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - MacMahon, Aline, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Magowan, Steve, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Malecot, Eric, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Mall, Rebecca, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Mamet, David, circa 1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Manley, Beatrice (1 of 2), 1974-2001 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Manley, Beatrice (2 of 2), 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manning, Lainie, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Manus, Willard, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Marcus, Sol, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Marguilies, Donald, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Marley, Sandra, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Marowitz, Charles (1 of 2), 1982-1997 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Marowtiz, Charles (2 of 2), 1983-2006 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Marsellos, Michael, circa 1990 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Martin, Malcolm, 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Mason, Marsha, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Mason, Shelly, 1980-1987 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Mason, Susan, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Masters, Roy, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - McAllister, Mary, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - McDermott, Tom, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - McEwan, Chaz, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - McFarland, Ron, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - McGuire, Michael, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - McLucas, Scott, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - McVicar, Scott, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Meade, Laurel, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Merrill, James, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Mersky, Kres, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Merwin, W. S., 1988 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Metzger, Deena, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Meyer, Michael, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Meyer, Nicholas (Visa), 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Micheal, Glenn, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Miller, Arthur. Timebends: A Life. New York: Grove Press, 1987. (Box 17)
    - Miller, Tim, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Milosz, Czeslaw, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Mitchell, John Cameron, 1991-2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Mizell, Mary, circa 1980 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Molina, Alfred, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Monette, Paul, 1988-1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Montoya, Jose, circa 1985 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Montz, Sidney, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Moore, Mark, circa 2000 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Morris, Steven, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Morrison, Toni, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Mount, Lisa, 1982-2006 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Mufson, Daniel, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Muske, Carol, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Myrow, Fred, 1984-1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Mardone, Diane, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Nass, Elyse, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Neame, Christopher, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Nelson, Doreen, 1994-2004 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Newmark, Paige, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Novak, Del, 1961-1964 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - O'Connor, Lenka Peterson, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - O'Connor, Tom, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - O'Dwyer, Caley, 1994-1997 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Ogawa, Tsohiro, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Olds, Sharon, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Olim, Dorothy, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Osborne, John, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Oster Elten, Gina, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - O'Sullivan, Michael, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Overbeck, Lois and Martha Fehsenfeld, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Overmeyer, Eric, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Pacht, Judith, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Paley, Grace, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Park, Muriel, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Pawlicki, Lawrence, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Peretz, Susan, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Perloff, Carey, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Perlstein, Michael J., 1987-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Perry, Stephen, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Peters, Brock, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Petrie, Bernard, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Petrie Hugenberg, Pat, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Phalen, Robert, 1985-1994 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Phipps, Jim, 1992-2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Picus, Joy, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Piercy, Marge, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Pierre, Dorathi Bock, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Pinero, Miguel, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Pinsky, Robert and Hollander, John, circa 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Pinter, Harold, 1985-2006 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Pointer, Priscilla and Symonds, Robert, 1987-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Quigley, Billy, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Rabb, Ellis, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Ragan, James, 1985-1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Rasile, Pat, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Rees, Roger, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Reiner, Annie, 1990-2001 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Reisz, Toby, circa 1988 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Rich, Adrienne, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Richard, Stephen, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Risk, Mary, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Rivera, Jon, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Robinson, Nan and Dave, 1997-2005 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Roche, Gene (Tribune), 2004 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Rodriguez Gago, Antonio, 1987-1995 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Roht, Ken, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Rolfe, Bari, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Rosenberg, Marv, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Rosenthal, Rachel, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Rossi, Al, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Roston, Ellen Knox, 1992-2002 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Roth, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Rudd, Paul, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Sagal, Peter, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Sanchez, Sonia, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Sargent, Michael, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Schaeffer, George, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Schembri, Julian Miller, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Schevill, James, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Schlosser, Robert, 1965-1988 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Schmidt, Doug, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Schwartz, Damon, 1997-2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Schweizer, David, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Scott, James and Shirley, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Scott, Leslie, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Seidler, David, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Selznick, Daniel (1 of 2), 1998-2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Selznick, Daniel (2 of 2), 1992-2011 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      Contains two letters from Daniel Selznick to Mandell that were inserted into Mandell's copy of Daniel's father's biography, Showman: The Life of David O. Selznick by David Thompson (Box 17). The first note is handwritten and from 1952. The second note is from June 18, 2011, and was written by Daniel as if he were Alan Mandell apologizing to "Danny." Mandell explains in an attached note, "This letter was written by Daniel Selznick. He sent it to me to chastise me for not thanking him for the theater tickets. I did thank him. He has a hearing problem, among other problems."
    - Sevilla, Jose, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Seyd, Richard, circa 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Shannon, Peggy, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Shawn, Wallace, 1981-1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Sheppard, Morgan, circa 1980 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Shiban, Theresa, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Silberman, Bob, circa 1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Silver, Anna, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Silvern, Bea, circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Simmons, James (Poetry), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Simkin, Daren, circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Simmons, Tom, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Simon, Mayo, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Simon, Roger Hendricks, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Sinner, John, 1996-2009 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Skaggs, Norman, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Skinner, Rupert, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Slagle, Susan, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Sloss, Nancy, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1980-1989 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Soch, Adam, 1999-2005 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Solari, Rudy, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Solov-Chabert, Sandra, 1989-1997 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Spender, Sir Stephen, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Stayton, Richard (1 of 2), 1989-2003 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Stayton, Richard (2 of 2), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Stegner, Wallace, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Steppling, John, 1991-2004 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Stern, Guy, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Stewart, Dean, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Stovall, Miriam, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Strand, Mark, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Strong, Brett Livingston, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Stross, Anne Heywood, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Subotnick, Morton, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Swanson, John, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Sykes, Arlene (Harold Pinter Materials), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Tate, James, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Taube, Louis, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Teitel, Carol, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Thalberg, Deborah, 1988-1999 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Tharp, Carol Baker, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Thomas, Morgan, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Thomson, David. Showman: The Life of David O. Selznick. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1992. (Box 17)
    - Thompson, Sada, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Tighe, Andy, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Tobin, Judith, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Tolins, Jonathan, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Trembley, Barbara (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Trembley, Barbara (2 of 2), 1995-2001 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Urios, Cristina, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - van Praag, Judith, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Viertel, Jack, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Vilar, Esther (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Vilar, Esther (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Vogel, Daniel (Photographer), undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Voznesensky, Andrei, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Wachtler, John, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Wade, Galen, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Walcott, Derek, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Waldman, Anne, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Walker, Alice, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Walker, Wesley, 1989-2007 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Wang, Yansong, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Wasserman, Dale, 1984-1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Wasserman, Ross, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Waxman, Rena, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Weinstein, David, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Wendt, George, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Whitelaw, Billie, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Wiederholt, Sven, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Willard, Nancy, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Williams, Barbara, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Wilson, Juan and Ginger, 1990-2002 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Wilson, Joyce Adrian, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Wolf, Carol, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Wu, Xiaojing (Central Experimental Theater, Beijing), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Yankee, Luke, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Yaroslavsky, Zev, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Yevtushenko, Yevgeny, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Zavala, Jorge Prado, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Zeigler, Joseph, 1981-1995 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Series 3: Theater Companies, 1952-1995
  Contains materials relating to the management of four different theater companies. Includes casts lists, correspondence, financial records, photographs, production schedules, press, programs, and more.
  - Subseries 3.1: San Francisco Actor's Workshop (SFAW), 1952-1965
    Scope and Content Note: Contains materials relating to both individual productions and the management of the Workshop as a whole. Includes documents relating to both the historic performance of Waiting for Godot in San Quentin Prison on November 19, 1957, and Jules Irving and Herbert Blau's controversial decision to leave the Workshop in 1965.
    - Death of a Salesman Photograph, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Audition Scripts, circa 1956 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - The Organization and Management of the Actor's Workshop of the San Francisco Drama Guild Incorporated by Ronald J. Bazarini, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Financial Documents, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - News Release, 1957-1963 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Children's Letters, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, circa 1960 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Reviews, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Sample Prospectus, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Subscription Brochures, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Budgets, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and Tickets, 1960-1969 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Various, 1961-1967 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Ford Foundation Grant, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Friedman and Son Photographs, 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Clippings, 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Arena Stage, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Stanford-Rockefeller Grant, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Theatre Party Contracts, circa 1960 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Payroll Schedule, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Children's Theatre of San Francisco (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Children's Theatre of San Francisco (2 of 2), circa 1963 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Actors' Equity Contract, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - The Amen Corner, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Ben Jonson's Volpone at Stanford, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Lowry Building Letter, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Workshop News Bulletin, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - News, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Thesis on American Theater and the San Francisco Actor's Workshop, circa 1970 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - San Francisco Theatre Article by Hal Gelb, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - San Francisco Actor's Workshop Retrospective, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Typescript with Notes by [Jules Irving] (1 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Typescript with Notes by [Jules Irving] (2 of 2), undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Photographs from "The Birds" and "Caucasian Chalk Circle" (Oversized), 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 3.2: San Quentin Drama Workshop (SQDW), 1957-1965
    Scope and Content Note: Contains scripts and other materials by and about Rick Cluchey, issues of the San Quentin News, photographs, press, and programs.
    - San Quentin News - Photographs, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - San Quentin News - Commemorative Edition, 1957-2008 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - San Quentin News - Issues, 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - In the Zone by Eugene O'Neill, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Various, 1963-1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Out At Sea - Technical Director's Copy, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Programs and Letters, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Playbill Article, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Gonsalves, Manny - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Cluchey, Rick - The Cage - Script, circa 1965 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Cluchey, Rick - The Cage - Barbwire Theatre Production, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Cluchey, Rick - The Cage - History, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Cluchey, Rick - Various, 1965-1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Cluchey, Rick - Beckett Directs Beckett (Samuel Beckett Materials), circa 1977 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Cluchey, Rick - From The Dead, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Bradby, David (Samuel Beckett Materials), 1993-2000 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - The Impossible Itself (Film) - Screening Press, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Croteau, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - The Iceman Cometh Commemorative Plaque (Oversized), 1964 June (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 3.3: Repertory Theatre of Lincoln Center (RTLC), 1965-1977
    Scope and Content Note: Contains records relating to the management of the Repertory and the productions put on by it in the late 1960s and early 1970s. Of particular interest for scholars of performances studies and race are the documents relating to the discrimination suit filed by a group of Asian-American actors against the Repertory (referred to as the "Oriental Actors" case). These include Jules Irving's internal memos about the case, lists of minority employees, a transcript of critic Clive Barnes's testimony, and the final decision of the New York Division of Human Rights in favor of the Repertory.
    - Blau and Irving in the New York Times, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Various, 1960-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Press Kit, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Herbert Blau and Jules Irving in the New York Times, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Clippings in Sleeves, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Inaugural Gala Publication, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - General, 1965-1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Programs, 1966-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Finances, 1967-1973 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Center History, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - Harris, Mark, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Actors' Equity Association, 1970-1973 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - "Oriental Actors" Discrimination Case, 1970-1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Dwight Frye Electrical, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Play Choices, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Statement of Financial Position, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Caedmon Records, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Beckett Plays (Samuel Beckett Materials), 1972 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Company Roster, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Costumes, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - A Streetcar Named Desire - Finances, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Center Theater Review, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 9)